OLES GEDZ

C++ DEVELOPER

Github:

https://github.com/olesgedz/

Email:

gedzoles@gmail.com

Phone:

+7(985) 948-98-42

Profile

Age: 25 years

I am studying at School 42, a computer graphics course. I have experience in leading a team of five people. I strive to gain new knowledge and implement my skills.

Achievements

Computer graphics

Creating a graphical editor based on path tracing technology.

School 42

Creation of projects such as: Ray Tracer, Rasterizer, Raycaster engine, Voxel engine.

Unity

- Participation in several projects of independent studios.
- Creation of a VR application for the practice of public speaking using data read from neural interfaces.
- Development of a VR platform for laboratory activities in university MEPhI.

Work experience

Constanta OSAI

C++ graphical engineer

Developing OpenGL engine for drawing animations on sport event live streams, using real-time data.

Sberbank Domclick

2021 - 2022

2022 - present

C++ Developer

Developing OpenGL ES renderer engine for bim models apartment rendering. Developing googlemaps style walking around engine for apartment, using opengles and openCV.

University MEPhI

2020 - 2021

Unity VR/AR Developer

Code Class
Programming C#, Unity and Mobile Development teacher

2017 - 2018

As a result of the training: the students created games of different genres using Unity.

Programming languages

C C#
C++ Python

Technologies:

 OpenCL
 Unity XR
 Docker

 OpenGL
 Unity Mars
 Git

 Vulkan
 Oculus intergration
 IBM Fabric

 Threads

 SDL

 Tensorflow

Education

 $School 42 - \mathbf{9.67}\,\mathbf{LVL}$

English - C2.

Incomplete higher education after two years of study at NUST MISIS, "Electronics and Nanomaterials".

Additional education Courses : Participation in the HSE summer school "Цифровая трансформация благотворительного сектора"

Coursera C++ by Moscow Institute of Physics and Technology, Yandex & E-Learning Development Fund UC San DiegoX: CSE167x Computer Graphics by Ravi Ramamoorth Computer Graphics with Modern OpenGL and C++ by Ben Cook

Gedz Oles — <u>gedzoles@gmail.com</u> —+7(985) 948-98-42